[
  {
   "question": "What can I build?",
    "answer": "Web, mobile, hardware, games, ... anything is on the table! Choose a challenge you like and build something cool. Other than a prototype, you will also have to present a small business plan for your project."
  },
  {
    "question": "Who can apply?",
    "answer": "Students from universities and high schools from all around the world. What The Hack is definitely not limited to computer science majors! Anyone who has an interest in technology and is eager to learn can participate."
  },
  {
    "question": "What if I can't code?",
    "answer": "No problem! You can still work on the idea, business plan, design and other aspects of your project. If you're interested in programming, you can also learn the basics at What The Hack. We'll have mentors and workshops to help you."
  },
  {
    "question": "What if I've never been to a hackathon before?",
    "answer": "What The Hack welcomes students of all skill levels. We’ll have mentors and workshops to help you with your project; hackathons can be a great place to learn new skills in a short amount of time. Just be eager to learn, and excited to meet lots of awesome people."
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the pitching work?",
    "answer": "On Saturday evening after the hacking you will have to present what you’ve built. You will get a couple of minutes to demo your prototype, and a couple of minutes to pitch your business plan."
  },
  {
    "question": "How big can teams be?",
    "answer": "Teams can have up to 5 participants. We advise you to have a balanced team of 3-4 developers, a business specialist and possibly a designer so you can present a working prototype and a business plan."
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I form my team?",
    "answer": "At the beginning of the event we will have a teambuilding moment, so you can form a balanced team. You can of course stick together with friends, but you will find that a mixed team with will be better. Moreover, part of the fun of a hackathon is meeting new people!"
  },
  {
    "question": "What about the schedule?",
    "answer": "Check-in will open at 17:30 on Friday March 1st. The opening ceremony starts at 18:00. You can work on your project from 19:00 on Friday until 19:00 on Saturday. Afterwards we will have presentations, and we expect to finish at 23:00 on Saturday March 2nd."
  },
  {
    "question": "What should I bring?",
    "answer": "All attendees must bring a valid government ID for admission. Other common checklist items include: laptops, chargers, adapters, sleeping bags and toiletries."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will there be travel reimbursements available?",
    "answer": "We will pay back your Belgian train tickets. Please make sure to keep the receipt so we can reimburse you."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I start working on my project before the event?",
    "answer": "No. In the interest of fairness, students should not be working on their projects before What The Hack begins and we do not allow participants to work on pre-existing projects. However, you can start thinking of ideas and familiarize yourself with all the tools and technologies you intend to use beforehand!"
  },
  {
    "question": "More questions?",
    "answer": "Send us an email at contact@whatthehack.be or message us on facebook.com/whatthehackleuven"
  }
]
